Owner should get org announce, org mute, and Partner Set verbs, along with the disband verb.
Partner Set would allow two org members to be paired together. While fighting on the same screen, or near each other, the partners would be granted a small willpower/struggle boost, in addition to a small boost to their stats.
Switch co-leader's benefits to leader, and allow the leader to decide which of the perks co-leader would get (either infilitrator, combatant, healer, or strategist), along with the leader verbs, excluding Disband.

GM-proof the org. If a player below the rank of owner attempts to teleport into the org map, have some message similar to 'A powerful force prevents you from entering this area.'. While the masks are equipped (once those are implemented), don't allow moderators to be able to see the player's key/real name. We'll give you and Sasuna the names of each member's masks, so if one abuses, there won't be a problem banning them.

________________________________
Space-Time Jutsu: 
A set of jutsu attached to the left and right hands. The power arises from a set of runes inscribed into the user's palms, reducting a permanent 100 vitality from the user, fifty from either hands. The jutsu themselves drain vitality and stamina, rather than chakra.


Freeze: Hands
- Used on a targeted opponent. If the target is forming handseals, the jutsu would be immediately cancelled. A message similar to '[charactername] glances at your hands. An outside force brings your handseals to a stop.'' would display
. Jutsu drains about 25 vitality.

Freeze: Legs
 - Used on a targeted opponent. Would gradually bring the target to a halt (would bring them from running to walking to eventually standing still). The target would be frozen for two seconds.
 'Your legs become onset with pressure; you come to a halt.' Drains about 35 vitality.

Freeze: Time - Would have three variations; target-centric, screen-wide, and map wide. The limits would vary from 15 to 10 to 5 seconds respectively. Could be struggled out of, to quicken the time frozen. The message 'The flow of time around you ceases.' would display. The jutsu drains a mixture of stamina and vitality, with the amount differing based on the form used. Target-centric would drain 20 vitality and 30 stamina, screen wide would drain 25 vitality and 45 stamina, and map wide would drain 50 vitality and 100 stamina.

Void: Inhale - Forces all mobs within a seven tile radius of the user to be sucked in towards the player.
 This attack costs 30 stamina.

Void: Exhale - Forcefully pushes all mobs within three tiles away. Could potentially cause wall damage.
 This attack costs 15 vitality and 35 stamina.

Void: Devour - The user opens up a single tile void on the tile they're standing on. Once this jutsu is used, the user would be stuck in place, and a steady chakra drain would occur. The void could expan up to a 5x5 square, and would suck in all jutsu and mobs within a three tile raidus. The jutsu would dissappear, while mobs dragged into it would be constantly damaged. The user can also double click jutsu in use to make them dissappear, while this jutsu is active. This attack costs 75 vitality and 125 stamina. 

Void: Transport - Used on a targeted player. Would slowly fade the target's screen to black, as if the player were going blind at a rapid rate. Once the screen was completely black, the user and the targeted player would be teleported to a black map, one screen large. On this map, the user of the jutsu would be able to teleport anywhere double-clicked. The stats of the user would be doubled during this time, as well. The players would reside on this map for ten seconds before being transported back to were they were previously. This attack drains a willpower from the user.
--------------------------------


Non-org related; 
Add in a 15% chance for legendary weapons to be dropped on death. Could give out the remaning ones that haven't been paid for through contests or other events; it would add more of a competitive element into the game.

Re-assign the Kyuubi, unless Bejii paid for a permanent version of it, or add in an artificial, weaker version of the Kyuubi.

Re-implement RPvP plsplspls Wouldn't require everybody to RP, obviously but just hosting random events that people could participate in, or assigning a person to would be awesome

Sasuna implemented the economy system; if you could add in my Festival suggestion, that'd be really cool.
-copied and pasted from suggestions file-
Event: Festival!
	Random event. Would have a lower chance of randomly being triggered. Could only occur randomly in Tea, though a kage of any village could forcibly host one (would have a 36 hour cooldown, at least). Hosting one would require it to be funded, either through the village pool or through the kage's own money. Any money acquired from the festival would be put back into the village, making it potentially beneficial, depending on its popularity. Would cost about 750,000 ryo to host.
		NPCs: Festivals would spawn several NPCs, mainly vendors, throughout the course of the festival.
		Food: Festivals would have 'carnival' foods. Cheap, unique foods that are high in calories, decently low in price (anywhere from 150-1000 ryo), and would perhaps boast a small boost as an incentive for players to buy them. Examples of carnival foods; fried macorini, fried oreos, candy apples, caramel apples, cotton candy, corn dogs, etc. All of these would, again, have massive amounts of calories, and maybe small boosts, like a temporary increase of stamina. Would be sold by various vendors.
		Activities: Add in activities for players to do.
			Brawls; players are spawned into a ring to fight. Would last until their first ko, they could only use their fists, all armor/weapons would be unequipped. 
			Plays; Add in more clothes/masks and shit, with a carnival-esque theme. Create a small theater, and allow those participating to wear the clothes belonging to a character, and RP out scenes with other players on stage.
			Shooting Range; Have targets and shit on the far side of the screen. They'd be stationary at first, but would begin to move over time. The player would be able to continue playing until they stacked up three misses; after which they'd be disqualified. For every hit, the player would gain about fifty points, and the player with the highest score would have their high score and name posted. The person with the highest score by the end of the festival could win a very small prize (like five ninja cash).
			Eating Contests; Would be partially based on the person's physique. Would essentially require spamming 'F' to shove food into their character's mouth. Would be slightly easier, the higher the person's physique was.
should have it like learnable to people with like 5K+ nin knowledge, at least 30 control, and taught by an NPC that can randomly spawn anywhere in the world, but should only have like a 40% chance of spawning at reboot.